https://www.brycoat.com/privacy-policy/

PVD Coatings
Titanium Nitride (TiN)
TiN Physical Properties
TiN for Erosion
Chromium Nitride (CrN)
CVD Coatings
Titanium Carbide (TIC)
Privacy Policy for Brycoat
If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at Privacy.
At https://www.brycoat.com we consider the privacy of our visitors to be extremely important. This privacy policy document describes in detail the types of personal information is collected and recorded by https://www.brycoat.com and how we use it.
Log Files Like many other Web sites, https://www.brycoat.com makes use of log files. These files merely logs visitors to the site – usually a standard procedure for hosting companies and a part of hosting services’s analytics. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and possibly the number of clicks. This information is used to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.
Personal information,including name, email address and phone number, may be collected through our contact form.
This information is used only for customer support. We do not sell or provide this information to third parties.
Cookies and Web Beaconshttps://www.brycoat.com does not use cookies.
If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites. What Are Cookies?
Online Privacy Policy Only
This privacy policy applies only to our online activities and is valid for visitors to our website and regarding information shared and/or collected there.
This policy does not apply to any information collected offline or via channels other than this website.
Consent
By using our website, you hereby consent to our privacy policy and agree to its terms.
UpdateThis Privacy Policy was last updated on: Friday, July 17th, 2015.
Should we update, amend or make any changes to our privacy policy, those changes will be posted here.
Coating Services
PVD Coatings
Titanium Nitride (TiN)
Chromium Nitride (CrN)
TiCN
TiAlN
Custom Coatings
PVD Coating Properties
Thermal Spray Coatings
Carbides
Ceramics
Abradable
CVD Coatings
Titanium Carbide (TiC)
TiC Coated Bearing Balls
Ask an Engineer
The Brycoat Advantage:
Large enough to meet your needsSmall enough to offer superior service
BryCoat Inc.
727-490-1000
•
Fax: 727-490-0233
207 Vollmer Avenue
•
PO Box 1976
•
Oldsmar, Florida 34677
Copyright © BryCoat Inc. All rights reserved. BryCoat and the BryCoat logo are Registered Trademarks of BryCoat Inc.
While BryCoat believes that the information contained in this website is accurate, no warranty is made on the accuracy of the data. The customer is responsible for testing properties that are critical to their application and for determining the suitability of any coating for the application.
Customer Terms & Conditions   •
Vendor Terms & Conditions  •
Privacy Policy   •
Sitemap
Site by Industrial Webworks
MENU
Home
About Us
Titanium Nitride (TiN)
TiN Physical Properties
TiN for Erosion
Chromium Nitride (CrN)
Titanium Carbide (TIC)
